Hi, I'm Chase. I'm going to go over my
A-Dartment auto-scoring dartboard.
It's mostly inspired by Autodarts,
and a lot of it was coded using Claude.
We got the Spartan to hold the darts,
that was found online.
And then I hand-drew the little
dashboard and scoreboard.
I need to import the records.
Let's go reset that.
Over here with the dartboard,
I 3D printed the different mounts.
They all hold a 32 by 32 camera
from Amazon.
Each one of the mounts
is a different iteration.
This one is the best. It has the lip
that hooks onto the ring around the edge.
Then it all wires down
to a Raspberry Pi down there.
The accuracy for scoring is 90-something.
Originally, I just had the detection of the darts,
and it just takes the different camera angles.
Eventually, I needed to implement a model to detect
the very tip of the dart and where it landed,
because when it got to the triples and on the edges,
it was hit or miss.
We'll go ahead and throw a couple.
That's 10.
16, 1.
So we got 15, 16, 1.
There's the 90% accuracy for you.
And then it switches over to Cade's turn.
Grab a couple darts.
Triple 20s, maybe? Just 20.
Five.
So that was 25 and 25.
Let's see what we got here. Hey, look at that.
25 and 25.
That is the A-Dartment auto-scoring project for you.